Andrew Moses

Location: Tempe, Arizona 85283 Phone: (480) 612-5250 Email: andrewmosesdrive@gmail.com

GitHub: http://bit.ly/2WyYNUo
Portfolio: https://bit.ly/3hcZY5e
LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/3hcZY5e

Full Stack Web Developer focused on creating unique, accessible, and user-friendly applications. Experienced team lead with a demonstrated history of success in leadership within the financial services and healthcare industries. Lifelong learner obsessed with finding a better way, taking on new challenges, and solving problems.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React, Amazon Web Services/Amplify, JavaScript, Node, Express, HTML5, CSS3, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, JawsDB, GraphQL, jQuery, Lodash, Materialize, Material UI, Spark Design Systems, Bootstrap, Webpack, Babel, Progressive Web Applications, Visual Studio, Git, Slack, Chrome DevTools, NPM, Heroku, CRUD, Agile Methodology, Unit Testing

PROJECTS

OnBoard - GitHub: http://bit.ly/3cPjMLD || **Deployment**: http://bit.ly/2YSJ1ET

Full-Stack application for onboarding new team members. Users can upload documents, review policies, manage tasks, and view training videos. Built with three other developers using Mongoose, Express, React, and Node.

Management ERP - *GitHub:* <u>https://bit.ly/2Kd62i7</u> || **Deployment**: <u>https://bit.ly/3mvrwDS</u> Full stack enterprise resource planning application built with three other developers using Node, Express-Handlebars, and Sequelize ORM. Deployed through Heroku.

Fitness Tracker - *GitHub*: <u>http://bit.ly/3h5rBwL</u> || *Deployment*: <u>https://bit.ly/3mATNJf</u>
Full stack application for creating, tracking, and logging workouts with persistence. Built with MongoDB,
Mongoose, Express, and Node. Deployed via Heroku.

EXPERIENCE

DevCore/Quicken Loans — *Trainer, Team Captain* || 2019 - Present

Leads new team members through intensive training on all areas of knowledge related to their future careers. Mentors and coaches new trainers as they develop their training skills.

- Awarded Top Executor in 2020
- Awarded MVP multiple times in 2020

Donor Network of Arizona — *Lead Recovery Coordinator* || 2011 - 2019

Directed teams of 3-5 individuals in highly adaptive situations with heavy time restrictions. Trained new and existing staff in all clinical positions and medical record/suitability review via EMR.

EDUCATION

University of Arizona — Full Stack Web Development Certificate 2019-2020 Scottsdale Community College — Associates Degree 2016 - 2018